<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sweets on Family Recipes</title>
    <link>https://julieboberg.github.io/Recipes/tags/sweets/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Sweets on Family Recipes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 10:35:37 -0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://julieboberg.github.io/Recipes/tags/sweets/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>No-Bake Peanut Butter Bars</title>
      <link>https://julieboberg.github.io/Recipes/post/peanut-butter-bars/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 10:35:37 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://julieboberg.github.io/Recipes/post/peanut-butter-bars/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 1/2 cup (115g) salted butter, melted 1 cup (120g) graham cracker crumbs (about 8 full sheet graham crackers) 2 cups (240g) confectioners’ sugar 1 cup + 2 Tablespoons (280g) creamy peanut butter, divided 1 cup (180g) semi-sweet chocolate chips Recipe Line an 8×8 or 9×9 inch square baking pan with aluminum foil or parchment paper. Set aside.
Mix the melted butter, graham cracker crumbs, and confectioners’ sugar together in a medium bowl.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Cardamom Cake</title>
      <link>https://julieboberg.github.io/Recipes/post/christmas-cardamom-cake/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 15:38:03 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://julieboberg.github.io/Recipes/post/christmas-cardamom-cake/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients Cake 1 lb. butter or margarine 2 cups light brown sugar 4 eggs 2 tsp vanilla 4 cups flour 2 tsp baking powder 2 ½ tsp baking soda ½ tsp salt 1 tbsp cardamom 2 cups sour cream Filling ¼ cup brown sugar 1 tbsp cinnamon ½ cup finely chopped pecans Recipe Preheat oven to 350. Oil bundt pan. Beat butter with sugar until light and fluffy. Add eggs, one at a time, beat well after each.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bunuelos</title>
      <link>https://julieboberg.github.io/Recipes/post/bunuelos/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 14:58:25 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://julieboberg.github.io/Recipes/post/bunuelos/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients Dough 3 cups of flour 1 tsp of salt Water Tomatillo leaves Syrup Piloncillo Cinnamon sticks Orange peels Recipe For dough, boil water with tomatillo husks for 15-20 minutes. Strain the husks out and let cool. Add water slowly to dry ingredients as needed. Roll dough into approximately a dozen balls. Let rest for 30 minutes. In a castiron skillet add water, cinnamon sticks, orange peels, and piloncillo. Simmer until piloncillo disolves.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
