<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Everyday on Family Recipes</title>
    <link>https://julieboberg.github.io/Recipes/tags/everyday/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Everyday on Family Recipes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 10:42:03 -0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://julieboberg.github.io/Recipes/tags/everyday/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>No-Knead Bread</title>
      <link>https://julieboberg.github.io/Recipes/post/no-knead-bread/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 10:42:03 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://julieboberg.github.io/Recipes/post/no-knead-bread/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 3 3/4 cups (450g) all purpose flour 1 1/2 cups (340g) water, lukewarm (~ 105 degrees) 1 1/2 teaspoon (9g) salt 2 1/4 teaspoons (7g) instant yeast or active dry yeast Recipe Combine all of the ingredients in a large mixing bowl, or a large food-safe plastic bucket.
Mix and stir everything together to make a very sticky, rough dough. If you have a stand mixer, beat at medium speed with the beater blade for 30 to 60 seconds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Instant Pot Lentil Soup</title>
      <link>https://julieboberg.github.io/Recipes/post/lentil-soup/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 10:30:02 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://julieboberg.github.io/Recipes/post/lentil-soup/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 1 medium yellow onion 3 medium celery stalks 3 medium carrots 3 cloves garlic 2 cups French or green lentils 1 teaspoon ground cumin 1 teaspoon ground coriander 1 teaspoon paprika 1 teaspoon kosher salt 1/4 teaspoon freshly ground black pepper 2 (32-ounce) boxes low-sodium vegetable or chicken broth 1 (15-ounce) can fire-roasted diced tomatoes 5 ounces baby spinach (about 5 packed cups) Recipe Prepare the following, placing them all in a 6-quart or larger Instant Pot or electric pressure cooker: Dice 1 medium yellow onion and 3 medium celery stalks, peel and cut 3 medium carrots into 1/2-inch thick rounds, and mince 3 garlic cloves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>White Chicken Chili</title>
      <link>https://julieboberg.github.io/Recipes/post/white-chicken-chili/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 10:11:12 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://julieboberg.github.io/Recipes/post/white-chicken-chili/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 2 (14.5-ounce) cans white beans 1 tablespoon canola oil 1 medium jalapeno pepper, minced 2 medium poblano peppers, chopped 1 large onion, chopped 4 garlic cloves, minced Kosher salt and freshly ground black pepper 1 tablespoon ground cumin 1 1/2 teaspoons ground coriander 1 teaspoon ancho chili powder 4 cups low-sodium chicken broth 2 limes, juiced, plus lime wedges, for serving 1 rotisserie chicken, skin removed and meat shredded 1/4 cup chopped cilantro leaves Sour cream, for topping Tortilla chips, coarsely crushed, for topping Recipe Drain and rinse the canned white beans.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
