<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Holidays on Family Recipes</title>
    <link>https://julieboberg.github.io/Recipes/tags/holidays/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Holidays on Family Recipes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 14:58:25 -0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://julieboberg.github.io/Recipes/tags/holidays/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Bunnuelos</title>
      <link>https://julieboberg.github.io/Recipes/post/bunnuelos/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 14:58:25 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://julieboberg.github.io/Recipes/post/bunnuelos/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients Dough 3 cups of flour 1 tsp of salt Water Tomatillo leaves Syrup Piloncillo Cinnamon sticks Orange peels Recipe For dough, boil water with tomatillo husks. Strain the husks out. Add water slowly to flour as needed. Roll dough into approximately a dozen balls. Let rest for 30 minutes. In a castiron skillet add water, cinnamon sticks, orange peels, and piloncillo. Simmer until piloncillo disolves. In a seperate skillet heat oil for frying.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oatmeal Chocolate Chip Cookies</title>
      <link>https://julieboberg.github.io/Recipes/post/oatmeal-chocolate-chip-cookies/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 14:43:30 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://julieboberg.github.io/Recipes/post/oatmeal-chocolate-chip-cookies/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 1 cup of brown sugar 1 cup of sugar 1 cup of butter 2 eggs 2 tsp vanilla 2 tbsp 1% milk 1 tsp baking soda 1 tsp baking powder 1 tsp salt 2 cups of flour 2 cups of quick oats Chocolate chips Walnuts (optional) Recipe Preheat oven to 350 degrees Beat butter and sugar in bowl until creamy. Add eggs, milk, and vanilla and mix until combined. Seperately combine flour, baking powder, baking soda, and salt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sugar Cookies</title>
      <link>https://julieboberg.github.io/Recipes/post/sugar-cookies/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 14:28:08 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://julieboberg.github.io/Recipes/post/sugar-cookies/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 1 cup butter 1 cup of sugar 1 large egg 1 tsp vanilla 2 tsp baking powder 3 cups of flour 3 tbsp milk Recipe Preheat oven to 400 degrees Beat butter and sugar in bowl until creamy. Add egg and vanilla. On low speed mix baking powder and flour into butter mixture until combined. Add milk and beat until dough collects around beaters (approx 2 minutes). Divide dough into thirds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cheesecake Thumbprint Cookies</title>
      <link>https://julieboberg.github.io/Recipes/post/cheesecake-cookies/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 11:05:05 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://julieboberg.github.io/Recipes/post/cheesecake-cookies/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients For the cheesecake filling 4 ounces cream cheese, softened 1/4 cup granulated sugar 1/8 teaspoon salt 1 large egg yolk 1 1/2 teaspoons sour cream 1/4 teaspoon vanilla For the cookie dough 16 tablespoons (1 cup) unsalted butter, softened 1/4 cup granulated sugar 1/4 teaspoon salt 1 large egg yolk 2 cups all-purpose flour Recipe In a mixing bowl, beat cream cheese until light and fluffy. Beat in sugar and salt until smooth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mushroom Gravy</title>
      <link>https://julieboberg.github.io/Recipes/post/mushroom-gravy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 11:05:05 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://julieboberg.github.io/Recipes/post/mushroom-gravy/</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 3/4 cup of chopped button mushrooms 1 small onion 1/4 cup butter 2.5 cups vegetable broth 2 tbsp soy sauce 1/4 cup of flour 1 tbsp poultry seasoning Salt &amp;amp; pepper to taste Recipe Melt butter in skillet and add onion and mushrooms.Saute for two minutes over high heat. Reduce to medium heat and add broth and soy sauce. Add flour slowly and stir. Bring to a simmer and reduce heat.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
